[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Ugh! I can't stand gym!
唉！我受不了健身房！
- Me neither. - Gym is the worst.
我也是。健身房最糟糕了。
- Yeah, Jim. Beat it.
是啊，Jim。走开。
- Not Jim--gym!
不是Jim——是健身房！
- Sorry, Jim.
对不起，Jim。
- It's okay.
没关系。
I hate gym too.
我也讨厌健身房。
- Dude, don't be so hard on yourself.
伙计，别对自己太苛刻。
- [sighs heavily]
[重重叹气]
You're supposed to be doing jumping jacks, kids.
你们应该在做开合跳，孩子们。
Those are... just jacks.
那些只是...普通的跳跃。
[kids moaning]
[孩子们呻吟]
- Is gym really so awful?
- 体育课真的那么糟糕吗？
- Well, Jim thinks so.
- 嗯，吉姆是这么认为的。
But we're working on that.
但我们正在努力改变这一点。
- Gym's just so pointless.
- 体育课就是毫无意义。
- So the thing I've dedicated my life to is pointless?
- 所以我一生奉献的事业是毫无意义的？
- Yeah, that about sums it up. - For the most part, yes.
- 是的，差不多就是这样。
- It's not your fault.
- 这并不是你的错。
Studies have shown that physical activity
研究表明，体育活动
just isn't as important as mental activity.
并不像脑力活动那样重要。
- Is that true? - Does it matter?
- 这是真的吗？ - 这重要吗？
We haven't had to do jumping jacks for 12 seconds.
我们已经12秒没有做开合跳了。
- Fine. I will give you a choice.
- 好吧。我给你一个选择。
For the rest of the year,
今年剩下的时间里，
do you want to do organized physical activity
你是想参加有组织的体育活动
that will benefit your health,
以促进你的健康，
or do what the Harpers are suggesting
还是按照哈珀家的建议
and just be left alone to fritter your lives away?
独自一人虚度光阴？
- We're gonna go with fritter.
- 我们选择消磨时光。
- Fine. That's it.
- 好吧。就这样。
I give up.
我放弃了。
I'm literally throwing in the towel.
我真的是举白旗了。
Thanks to the Harpers,
多亏了哈珀一家，
you are free to fritter.
你们可以自由地消磨时间了。
[all cheering]
[众人欢呼]
- Nice! - Harpers!
- 太好了！ - 哈珀一家！
all: ♪ We are free to fritter ♪
♪ 我们可以自由地消磨时光 ♪
♪ Fritter, fritter, fritter ♪
♪ 消磨，消磨，消磨 ♪
♪ We are free to fritter ♪
♪ 我们自由地消磨时光 ♪
- Why aren't you frittering?
你为什么不消磨时光？
- Um, I'm frittering in my own way.
嗯，我在以我自己的方式消磨时光。
- Those are my rockets.
那些是我的火箭。
You can't tape them to your skateboard.
你不能把它们粘在你的滑板上。
- I know.
我知道。
That's why I taped them to your skateboard.
那正是我把它们粘在你滑板上的原因。
- Well, it's not safe.
好吧，这不安全。
Use your brain.
用用你的脑子。
- I'm wearing a helmet.
我戴着头盔。
- That is also my helmet!
- 那也是我的头盔！
- Careful, kids.
- 小心点，孩子们。
Just taking down this "Physical Fitness Matters" banner.
只是要把这个“体育锻炼很重要”的横幅拆下来。
Because apparently, it doesn't.
因为显然，它不重要。
- What's the big deal?
- 有什么大不了的？
You never use your skateboard anyway.
反正你从来不用你的滑板。
- Sure I do!
- 当然我用！
In fact, I'm going to use it right now!
事实上，我现在就要用！
- Well, you better take your precious helmet
- 那你最好带上你珍贵的头盔
so you don't hurt the brain you like to use.
以免伤到你喜欢用的脑子。
- Well, at least my brain isn't dumb enough
好吧，至少我的脑子还没笨到
to be on this board when those rockets go off.
在这火箭发射时还站在这板上。
- Hey, guys, join the fritter line.
嘿，伙计们，加入排队吧。
- I'll fritter with you.
我会和你一起排队的。
[rockets blasting]
[火箭发射]
- Whoa!
哇！
- Whuh-uhhhh!
哇-啊-啊！
[crash]
[撞击]
- [gasping]
[喘气]
I'm fine! I'm fine.
我没事！我没事。
- I'm not.
我不行。
- It was a wig!
那是假发！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪♪
- Who was responsible for this?
- 这是谁干的？
- It... was... the... Harp...
- 是...那...竖...琴...
- [chuckling] Well, you heard him, Principal Tarian.
- [轻笑] 好吧，你听到了，塔里安校长。
It was the harp.
是竖琴。
- I knew we shouldn't have stored the band equipment
- 我就知道我们不该把乐队设备存放在体育馆。
in the gym.
在体育馆。
Well, you kids stay away from that harp
好吧，你们这些孩子离那竖琴远点
while I call in a substitute.
我打电话叫个替补来。
I hope Mr. McGee is available.
希望麦吉先生有空。
all: Pull-Ups McGee?!
所有人: 拔河麦吉？！
- Let's warm up...
- 让我们热身...
with a set of 50.
做一组50个。
- We're never gonna survive Pull-Ups McGee.
- 我们绝不可能在Pull-Ups McGee手下存活。
- First you gave us frittering,
- 先是给了我们frittering，
and then you took it away!
- 然后又把它夺走了！
- I wish I'd never known frittering at all.
- 我真希望我从不知道frittering是什么。
- You need to fix this, Harpers.
- 你们需要解决这个问题，Harpers。
- Okay, hold on!
- 好的，稍等！
When have we ever let you down?
我们什么时候让你们失望过？
- I have a list in my locker.
- 我的储物柜里有一份清单。
- Very funny. - No, he actually has a list.
- 非常有趣。 - 不，他真的有一份清单。
- I've seen it. It's not short.
- 我见过。它并不短。
- Fix this, Harpers. [angry muttering]
- 解决这个问题，Harpers。[愤怒的咕哝]
♪♪
- I know I promised to play ball with you, Shelley,
- 我知道我答应过和你一起打球，Shelley，
but I need this list of Phys. Ed. substitutes!
但我需要这份体育替代教师的名单！
Okay.
好的。
Mwah.
亲一下。
Okay.
好的。
- Now, now, let's not be hasty.
- 现在，现在，我们不要急躁。
Pull-Ups McGee got the call the last time Coach Fessler was out.
上次费斯勒教练不在时，是普尔-阿普·麦吉接的电话。
- Don't you think our hungry young minds
- 你不觉得我们饥渴的年轻心灵
deserve variety in our educators?
需要教育者的多样性吗？
- I mean, McGee is McGood,
- 我是说，麦吉已经很好了，
but why not go for McGreat?
但为什么不追求更卓越的呢？
- Or McAnyone Else.
- 或者其他人。
- Or...
- 或者...
that guy.
那个人。
- Ooh. - Yes!
- 哦。 - 是的！
- McPerfect.
- 完美人选。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
- Tom's Get Sporty. This is Tom.
- Tom's Get Sporty. 我是Tom。
Yes, sir, Principal Tarian, sir.
是的，先生，Tarian校长，先生。
I'm your man.
我是您的合适人选。
Y-you can count on me!
您可以依靠我！
Guess what, Anne?
猜猜看，Anne？
They need a substitute gym teacher and they...
他们需要一个代课体育老师，而且他们...
they asked me!
他们找了我！
- You?
- 你？
That's... great, Tom.
那真是...太好了，Tom。
- Do I detect a hint of jealousy?
- 我感觉到一丝嫉妒的气息吗？
- No, no, no. No, just, you know...
- 不，不，不。不是的，只是你知道...
just wondering why they didn't ask me.
- 只是好奇为什么他们没有问我。
- Oh. - We're both qualified P.E. subs
- 哦。 - 我们都是合格的体育代课老师
and my name is first alphabetically.
- 而我的名字按字母顺序排在前面。
Anne comes before Tom.
- Anne排在Tom前面。
- Yes, well, that's because I told them my name
- 是的，那是因为我告诉他们我的名字
was Aaamazing Tom.
- 是Aaamazing Tom。
- [gasps] - With three A's.
- [吸气声] - 有三个A。
To come higher on the lists. - [gasps loudly]
- 为了在名单上排得更靠前。 - [大声吸气声]
That's cheating!
那是作弊！
- Is it, Anne?
是吗，Anne？
Or does it show who has
还是说这显示了谁
a stronger desire to teach?
有更强烈的教学欲望？
- I'm gonna go with cheater.
我会说是作弊者。
- I'm gonna go with jealous.
我会说是嫉妒。
- Cheater. - Jealous.
作弊者。
- Cheater! - Jealous.
嫉妒。
- Customer! - Jealous.
作弊者！
- Customer.
嫉妒。
He's a cheater.
他是骗子。
- She's just jealous. - Cheater!
她只是嫉妒。 - 骗子！
[upbeat music]
- I don't know.
我不知道。
Are we sure inviting Dad
我们确定邀请爸爸
to spend any more time in our lives
在我们的生活中多花时间
is a good idea?
是个好主意吗？
- It's gonna be a little embarrassing to have him as a teacher,
让他当老师会有点尴尬，
but at least the whole class won't be mad at us.
但至少全班不会对我们生气。
- Besides, Dad is such a people-pleaser, all we have to do is push the right buttons
而且，爸爸很会讨好人，我们只需要按对按钮
to make sure he pleases the right people.
确保他取悦了正确的人。
- Namely us.
特别是我们。
- Hey, kids! I can't wait till tomorrow.
嘿，孩子们！我迫不及待到明天了。
- Cheater! - Jealous!
作弊者！ 嫉妒！
- I am so excited to physically educate you and your friends.
我非常兴奋能亲自教育你和你的朋友们。
Hey, check out my lesson plan.
嘿，看看我的教案。
- Lesson plan? - [high-pitched] Lesson plan?
教案？
- [higher-pitched] Lesson plan?!
- I can't go that high,
我不能唱那么高，
so I'm just gonna start us over.
所以我打算从头开始。
[deeply] Lesson plan?
[深沉地] 教案？
- What's wrong with a lesson plan?
- 教案有什么问题吗？
- [laughs] You don't need one.
- [笑] 你不需要教案。
- But I want to be just like your regular teacher.
- 但我想像你平时的老师那样。
- Then you definitely don't need one.
- 那你肯定不需要教案。
- Uh, yeah, Coach Fessler has this new, innovative curriculum
- 嗯，费斯勒教练有一个新的、创新的课程
that everybody loves.
大家都喜欢。
He calls it "kick back and chill."
他称之为“放松和冷静”。
- Oh. Kickball and chill. Gotcha.
- 哦。踢球和冷静。明白了。
- No ball. Back.
- 没有球。放松。
Kick back...
放松...
- And chill.
- 放松。
- Hey there, Squish. All right.
- 嘿，Squish。好吧。
This doesn't seem like exercise.
这看起来不像是在锻炼。
[together] Exactly.
[一起] 正是如此。
♪♪
- Hey! This better be good, Harpers.
- 嘿！这最好是有好处的，Harpers。
[together] It will be.
[一起] 会的。
- Good morning, students.
- 早上好，同学们。
You may know me as the Tom
你们可能知道我是Tom
from Tom's Get Sporty.
来自Tom的Get Sporty。
Check us out online.
在网上查看我们。
But today, I'm Mr. Harper.
但今天，我是Harper先生。
And I'm gonna teach you...
而我将要教你们...
to kick back...
放松...
and chill.
和冷静。
- This is great.
- 这太棒了。
- You saved gym class.
- 你拯救了体育课。
- Yeah, and he's not even embarrassing us.
- 是的，他甚至没有让我们感到尴尬。
- Now, I don't know how you guys kick back and chill,
- 现在，我不知道你们怎么放松和冷静，
but this is how I do it.
但这是我放松的方式。
[exhales]
（呼气声）
Whoo!
哇！
- Sorry about the short shorts.
抱歉穿了短裤。
- No, your dad's hilarious.
不，你爸爸真有趣。
- Good job, Harpers.
干得好，哈珀家的人。
Looks like I got to scratch this off the list.
看来我可以从清单上划掉这一项了。
- Told you we'd handle it.
告诉过你会搞定的。
- What are you kids standing around for?
你们这些孩子还站着干嘛？
Get to kickin' and chillin'.
开始踢球和放松吧。
- Yeah. - Yeah!
- 是的。 - 是的！
- Let's conga!
- 我们来跳康加舞吧！
all: ♪ We are kickin' and chillin' ♪
大家: ♪ 我们在踢腿和放松 ♪
♪ Chillin', chillin', chillin' ♪
♪ 放松，放松，放松 ♪
- Hey, if those shorts are the worst he's got,
- 嘿，如果那些短裤是他最糟糕的装备，
we're golden.
我们就稳赢了。
[harp resonates]
[竖琴共鸣]
♪ ♪
- Okay, shorts and a harp.
- 好吧，短裤和竖琴。
We can live with that.
我们可以接受这个。
- ♪ Ave ♪
♪ 万福 ♪
♪ Maria ♪
♪ 玛利亚 ♪
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Unbelievable.
难以置信。
- [laughs] Just wait till you hear what happens next.
[笑] 等着听接下来发生的事吧。
- Uh, she made, uh...
呃，她做了，呃...
hey, you're just in time for the best part.
嘿，你来得正是时候，最精彩的部分。
Uh, make that face you made when you were three
呃，做出你三岁时在五金店展示马桶里拉便便时的表情。
and you pooped in the display toilet at the hardware store.
没错，就是那个表情！你看到了吗？
Yup, that's the face! You see it?
你看到了吗？[笑]
Did you see it? [laughing]
- Dawn, why are you making "hardware store poop face"?
- 道恩，你为什么在做“五金店拉屎脸”？
- We have a serious problem.
- 我们有个严重的问题。
- [snorts] Yeah, you said that at the hardware store.
- [笑] 是的，你在五金店也这么说过。
- No! This is a big mess.
- 不！这是个烂摊子。
- You said that too.
- 你也这么说过。
- Dad just told everybody that story.
- 爸爸刚刚把那个故事告诉了所有人。
[all laughing]
[大家都笑]
- It's not funny!
- 这不好笑！
We have to do something.
我们必须做点什么。
- Sorry, Dawn, but I don't see how this affects us.
对不起，Dawn，但我不明白这怎么会影响到我们。
- If you like that one, wait'll you hear about the time
如果你觉得那个好笑，那你得听听那次
the boys' bathing suits fell off at the water park.
男孩们在水上乐园泳裤掉下来的事。
[yelps]
（惊叫声）
[laughter]
（笑声）
- This is wildly uncomfortable.
这真是太尴尬了。
- That's what you said at the water park.
那次在水上乐园你也是这么说的。
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是啊 ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- So Nicky, Ricky, and Dicky
所以Nicky，Ricky和Dicky
were standing at the top of the water slide.
站在滑水道的顶端。
Now, I told them, "Make sure you tie your suits," right?
现在，我告诉他们，“确保你们绑好泳衣，”对吧？
- We have to stop him!
- 我们必须阻止他！
- Um, Mr. Harper,
- 嗯，哈珀先生，
a word.
说句话。
- To be continued.
- 未完待续。
- Dad, why are you telling them these stories?
- 爸爸，你为什么要给他们讲这些故事？
- I was just kickin' back and chillin'.
- 我只是放松一下，享受一下。
- No, we do the kickin' back and chillin'.
- 不，我们才是放松和享受的。
You do the standin' and watchin'.
你负责站着看。
- Remember, you're the teacher.
记住，你是老师。
Don't be so buddy-buddy with everybody.
不要和每个人都那么亲密无间。
- Too buddy-buddy. Gotcha.
太亲密了。明白了。
[relieved sighs]
[松了一口气]
Line up!
排队！
All right.
好的。
This... is a squat thrust.
这个...是蹲跳。
First you squat...
首先你蹲下...
and then you thrust.
然后你跳起。
- What did you do to him?
你对他做了什么？
- Don't worry. We got this.
别担心，我们搞得定。
Mr. Harper, another word.
哈珀先生，再说一个词。
- What are you doing?!
你在干什么？！
- What? You said I was too buddy-buddy.
什么？你说过我太友好了。
- Now you're too squatty-thrusty!
现在你又太蹲推了！
- First you were too soft, and now you're too hard.
一开始你太软弱，现在又太强硬。
We need you to be just right.
我们需要你恰到好处。
- Got it. I know just what to do.
明白了，我知道该怎么做。
- Okay.
好的。
Don't worry. We fixed it.
别担心，我们解决了。
- Okay, class, I think I have an activity
好的，同学们，我想我有一个活动
that's juuuust right.
刚刚好。
Kids, your Goldilocks story reminded me of something
孩子们，你们的金发姑娘故事让我想起了一些
we used to do when you were little.
你们小时候我们常做的事情。
- What is he doing?
他在做什么？
- Dawn and her brothers are gonna show you a little game
Dawn和她的兄弟们将要给你们展示一个
we used to play in our house called...
我们以前在家里玩的小游戏，叫做...
[together] Uh-oh.
哎呀。
- Meow-Meow. - Oh, no.
喵喵。
- [high-pitched] Oh, no. - [higher-pitched] Oh, no!
哦，不。
- [deeply] Oh, no.
- [深沉] 哦，不。
- What's Meow-Meow?
- 什么是“喵喵”？
- It's nothing.
- 没什么。
- Ah, ah.
- 啊，啊。
You didn't think it was nothing when you were six.
- 你六岁的时候可不觉得它没什么。
Come on, show 'em how it's done.
- 来吧，展示给他们看怎么做。
- I'd rather do pull-ups.
- 我宁愿做引体向上。
- Oh, come on. - Show us how it's done.
- 哦，来吧。
- See? Everyone wants Meow-Meow.
- 展示给我们看怎么做。
Yup, Meow-Meow...
- 看？大家都想要“喵喵”。
[all chanting] Meow-Meow! Meow-Meow!
[众人齐声] 喵喵！喵喵！
Meow-Meow! Meow-Meow!
喵喵！喵喵！
- Mae, you too?
- 梅，你也来吗？
- Sorry, Dawn.
- 对不起，道恩。
I got to see this.
我得看看这个。
- On your mark, get set...
- 各就各位，准备...
Meow-Meow!
喵喵！
[together] Meow, meow, meow, meow...
[一起] 喵，喵，喵，喵...
Meow, meow...
喵，喵...
- Meow! Meow!
- 喵！喵！
Meow! Meow!
喵！喵！
Bathe those paws! Bathe those paws!
洗洗那些爪子！洗洗那些爪子！
Bathe those paws, bathe those paws.
洗洗那些爪子，洗洗那些爪子。
Bat that yarn. Bat that yarn.
打那团毛线。打那团毛线。
Come on. There you go.
来吧。就是这样。
[together] Meow, meow, meow. Meow, meow, meow.
喵，喵，喵。喵，喵，喵。
- What have we done?
我们做了什么？
- He's literally ruining our lives.
他简直在毁掉我们的生活。
- At least our friends are happy.
至少我们的朋友们很开心。
- Everybody Meow-Meow!
大家都喵喵！
Paws up, kittens. Come on, let's go.
举起爪子，小猫们。来吧，我们走。
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow...
喵，喵，喵，喵，喵...
all: Meow. Meow. Meow.
全体：喵。喵。喵。
- This is all your fault, Harpers.
- 这都是你的错，哈珀斯。
[together] Harpers?!
[一起] 哈珀斯？！
- She never calls us Harpers.
- 她从没叫我们哈珀斯。
all: Meow. Meow. Meow.
全体：喵。喵。喵。
[hissing]
[嘶嘶声]
- These kitties have claws!
- 这些小猫有爪子！
- [screaming]
- [尖叫声]
- ♪ Oh, oh, ay ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哎 ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh-oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦-哦，哦 ♪
- Of the 4,762 days we've been alive,
在我们活过的4,762天里，
this is the worst.
这是最糟糕的一天。
- Everyone at school wants our heads.
学校里的每个人都想要我们的命。
- Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
Chicken pot pie is almost ready.
鸡肉馅饼快做好了。
[humming] [laughs]
哼唱声 笑声
- What's so funny?
有什么好笑的？
- Can't say.
不能说。
Cat's got my tongue.
猫儿把我的舌头叼走了。
I'm sorry, I just can't believe that your dad
对不起，我只是无法相信你爸爸
made the whole class play Meow-Meow.
让全班同学玩喵喵。
He actually had you and all of your friends
他真的让你和你所有的朋友
prance around the gym like widdle kitties.
像小猫咪一样在体育馆里蹦蹦跳跳。
[purrs]
（发出呼噜声）
- Stop making us relive it!
别让我们再经历那件事了！
Oh! Ha. If I were your teacher,
哦！哈。如果我是你的老师，
I would never make you play such a childish game.
我绝不会让你玩这么幼稚的游戏。
- [sighs] Too bad you're not on the substitute list.
可惜你不在代课名单上。
- Oh, but I am, my little kittens.
哦，但我确实在名单上，我的小猫咪们。
- Too soon, Mom.
太快了，妈妈。
- Wait, if you were on the list,
等等，如果你在名单上，
your name would alphabetically come before Dad's.
你的名字会按字母顺序排在爸爸之前。
- Ah, you would think so,
啊，你可能会这么想，
but you would also think
但你也可能会认为
that your father wasn't a cheater!
你爸爸不是个骗子！
- Jealous!
嫉妒！
- Oh, well, guess you're stuck with Mr. Meow-Meow.
哦，好吧，看来你只能忍受喵喵先生了。
- Yeah.
是啊。
- Even though... I'm on the list.
- 尽管...我在名单上。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- And I could be your teacher.
- 我甚至可以成为你的老师。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Do you see where I'm going with this?
- 你明白我的意思吗？
- No.
- 不。
- [sighs] - Wait a minute.
- [叹气] - 等一下。
You could be our teacher! - [gasps]
你可以成为我们的老师！ - [吸气声]
Wait, no. Me?
等等，不。我？
But how would that even be possible?
但这怎么可能呢？
I mean, your dad already has the job.
我是说，你爸爸已经得到这份工作了。
[together] Yeah.
[一起] 是的。
- Unless he didn't.
- 除非他没有。
- What does that mean?
- 那是什么意思？
[together] Ahhh.
[一起] 啊。
- Nope, nothing. - Not a clue.
- 不，没什么。 - 一点头绪都没有。
- I just went "ahh" because they did.
- 我只是因为他们说了“啊”所以我也说了。
- I'm just saying you guys got him the job,
- 我的意思是，是你们让他得到这份工作的，
so I'm sure you could un-get him the job.
所以我相信你们也能让他失去这份工作。
- But how would we do that?
- 但我们该怎么做呢？
- Gosh, I don't have to tell you what to do.
- 天哪，我不需要告诉你该怎么做。
Just Quaddle up, plot something, and take care of business.
只要动动脑筋，策划一下，然后处理好事情。
[together] Right.
[一起] 对。
[murmuring]
[低语]
- We need you to tell us what to do.
- 我们需要你告诉我们该怎么做。
- [sighs] For goodness sakes.
- [叹气] 看在上帝的份上。
[whispering] Get your dad fired.
[耳语] 让你爸爸被解雇。
[together] Ahhh.
[一起] 啊。
- Then who will teach us?
- 那谁来教我们呢？
- Arrrgh.
- 啊。
- She means we should get Dad fired and Mom hired.
- 她的意思是我们应该让爸爸被解雇，妈妈被雇佣。
[timer dings] - Now I get it.
[计时器响] - 现在我明白了。
- Looks like the chicken plot pie is ready.
- 看起来鸡肉馅饼准备好了。
- Okay, but just remember, what gets plotted in the kitchen
- 好的，但请记住，厨房里策划的事情
stays in the kitchen.
就留在厨房里。
This conversation never happened.
这场对话从未发生过。
- What conversation?
- 什么对话？
- Ugh, the one we just had
- 呃，就是我们刚刚
where Mom told us to get Dad fired and her hired.
妈妈告诉我们要让爸爸被解雇，她被雇佣的那场对话。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪啦，啦，啦，啦，啦♪
[all meowing]
[全部喵喵叫]
- All right!
- 好了！
Shelly and I have seen enough.
- 我和Shelly已经看够了。
I grant you it's embarrassing,
- 我承认这很尴尬，
but I don't know if making you play Meow-Meow
- 但我不确定让你扮演喵喵
is a fire-able offense.
- 是否是解雇的理由。
- Um, he also said turtles are stupid pets.
- 呃，他还说乌龟是愚蠢的宠物。
- He's gone.
- 他完蛋了。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪啦，啦，啦，啦♪
[blasts whistle]
[吹哨]
- Line up, everybody.
- 排好队，各位。
I'm Ms. Harper. And I know I'm new,
我是哈珀老师。我知道我是新来的，
but I am hoping that I will
但我希望我能
"work out" better than your last teacher.
比你们之前的老师表现得好。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Not her best material,
- 不是她最好的段子，
but at least we're not lapping up milk.
但至少我们不用舔牛奶。
- Yeah.
是的。
Hey, getting Dad fired and Mom hired
嘿，让老爸被解雇，老妈被聘用是我们能做的最棒的事了。
was the best thing we could've ever done.
是啊。
- Yeah. - Ms. Harper's kinda cute.
哈珀老师有点可爱。
- Smokin' cute.
超级迷人。
- That's our mom!
那可是我们妈妈！
- No, your mom is Mrs. Harper.
不，你妈是哈珀太太。老师是哈珀小姐。
The teacher is Ms. Harper.
发生了什么？
- What's going on?
他们刚刚为老妈击拳庆祝了。
They just fist-bumped over Mom.
不准为我们的老妈击拳！
- There will be no fist-bumping over our mom!
- 我们妈妈可不允许这样击拳！
- Yeah. You met our mom a thousand times.
- 对啊，你见我们妈妈都见了一千次了。
- Yeah, but she's never worn a whistle before
- 是啊，但她以前从没戴过哨子，
and told us what to do.
- 也没指挥过我们做什么。
- Okay, I'm gonna need a volunteer to hold my feet
- 好吧，我需要一个志愿者来帮我扶住脚，
while I demonstrate a proper sit-up.
- 我示范一下正确的仰卧起坐。
- Excuse me while I demonstrate a proper throw-up.
- 不好意思，我得示范一下正确的呕吐。
♪♪
- It's so weird that they think Mom's cute.
- 他们觉得妈妈可爱，真是太奇怪了。
- I don't see it.
- 我看不出哪里可爱。
- Why are you looking for it?!
- 你找什么呢？！
- Let's not overreact.
- 别太激动。
Maybe it's just an "at school" thing.
可能只是在学校里才这样吧。
[doorbell chimes]
[门铃响]
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，伙计们。
- Is Ms. Harper around?
- 哈珀女士在吗？
- Okay, Ms. Harper has got to go.
- 好吧，哈珀女士得走了。
- Just one thing first.
- 先说一件事。
What? Free chocolates.
什么？免费的巧克力。
- Okay, we have to think of a plan to get Mom fired.
好的，我们得想个办法让妈妈被解雇。
- Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
Do you have any idea who told Principal Tarian
你们知道是谁告诉塔里安校长
that I think turtles are stupid pets?
我认为乌龟是愚蠢的宠物吗？
[muttering incoherently]
[含糊不清地嘟囔]
I think it might've been your mother.
我觉得可能是你妈妈。
- No! [muttering]
不！[嘟囔]
- So it was her!
所以是她！
Your mother's a wonderful woman,
你妈妈是个了不起的女人，
but she does not like to lose.
但她不喜欢输。
I admire her competitive spirit,
我钦佩她的竞争精神，
even though she's a cheater!
即使她是个作弊者！
- Jealous! - She's right, I am jealous.
- 嫉妒！ - 她说得对，我确实嫉妒。
Eh, if you want your old teacher back,
如果你想找回你以前的老师，
you know where to find him.
你知道去哪儿找他。
In the kitchen...
在厨房里...
Eating chocolates.
吃巧克力。
- Dad's right.
- 爸爸说得对。
We need to get our old teacher back.
我们需要找回我们以前的老师。
- But he took our chocolates.
- 但他拿走了我们的巧克力。
- Not Dad!
- 不是爸爸！
Coach Fessler!
费斯勒教练！
And if you really want more chocolates...
而且如果你真的想要更多巧克力...
- And the bear.
- 还有那只熊。
- Happy?
- 高兴吗？
- You are bear-y special, Ms. Harper.
- 你真是特别的小熊，哈珀小姐。
- Nope.
- 不。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- Uh, excuse us.
- 呃，打扰一下。
We're looking for Coach Fessler.
我们在找费斯勒教练。
- Sorry, kids. You're too late.
抱歉，孩子们，你们来晚了。
- Too late? Where is he?
来晚了？他在哪儿？
- He's gone.
他已经走了。
- What, you mean he's gone home?
什么，你是说他回家了？
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
He's gone to the big gym upstairs.
他去了楼上那个大健身房。
- Guess he won't need this pudding cup.
看来他不需要这个布丁杯了。
Ow.
哎哟。
- You never eat another man's pudding.
你不能吃别人的布丁。
Especially when he's gone to the big gym upstairs.
尤其是当他去了楼上的大健身房。
- Seems like a perfect time to eat his pudding.
- 看起来是吃他布丁的完美时机。
Don't you think that's what he would've wanted?
你不觉得那正是他想要的吗？
- I think he would've wanted to be here to eat his own pudding.
- 我想他更希望自己在这里吃自己的布丁。
- I can't believe he's gone.
- 我简直不敢相信他走了。
- What are we gonna do?
- 我们该怎么办？
He's never coming back.
他再也不会回来了。
- I'm gonna miss him. - Me too.
- 我会想念他的。 - 我也是。
- He was the best gym teacher we ever had.
- 他曾是我们遇到过的最好的体育老师。
And we just frittered our time away.
而我们只是虚度了光阴。
- I wish he was here so we could tell him that we were wrong.
我希望他在这里，这样我们就可以告诉他我们错了。
- [sniffs] Smells like he's still here.
闻起来他好像还在这里。
I just got a whiff of that tangy mix
我刚刚闻到了那种混合的酸味
of cheap cologne and old sweat.
廉价古龙水和旧汗的味道。
- And garlic. He ate a lot of garlic.
还有大蒜。他吃了很多大蒜。
- If you can hear us, Coach...
如果你能听到我们，教练...
we're sorry.
我们很抱歉。
Physical fitness does matter.
身体健康确实很重要。
- I can hear you.
我能听到你们。
[all scream]
（所有人尖叫）
- He's a ghost!
- 他是鬼！
- You're the best teacher ever, Ms. Harper.
- 你是最好的老师，哈珀女士。
- Did you re-gift this?
- 你这是转送礼物吗？
- No...
- 不是...
Ms. Harper.
- 哈珀女士。
- You're alive? - Of course I'm alive.
- 你还活着？ - 当然我还活着。
- But the nurse told us that you went to the big gym upstairs.
- 但护士告诉我们你去了楼上的大健身房。
- I did. There's a big gym on the 12th floor.
- 我是去了。12楼有个大健身房。
[together] Ohhh.
[一起] 哦hhh。
- I'm being discharged later, so before I head home,
- 我晚些时候要出院，所以在回家之前，
I wanted to sweat out some of this garlic.
我想用汗水排掉一些大蒜味。
- Well, mission accomplished.
好吧，任务完成了。
- Wait, you're going home?
等等，你要回家了？
Does that mean you'll be back at school tomorrow?
那是不是意味着你明天会回学校？
- [laughs] Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
哈哈，那是不可能的。
Now let me eat my pudding in peace.
现在让我安静地吃我的布丁。
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
是啊，那是不可能的。
It's what you would've wanted.
这是你想要的。
- But you're coming back eventually, right?
但你最终会回来的，对吧？
- Actually, no.
实际上，不会。
I'm thinking of retiring.
我正在考虑退休。
- Retiring?!
退休？！
You can't do that.
你不能那样做。
Didn't you hear all the nice things we said about you?
你没听到我们说的那些关于你的好话吗？
- You just said those 'cause you thought I went to
你只是说那些因为你以为我去了
the big gym upstairs.
楼上的大健身房。
- Yeah, but point is we said them.
是啊，但重点是我们说了。
- And we meant most of them.
而且我们大部分都是真心的。
- Did you mean the one about physical fitness matters?
你是指关于身体健康很重要的那一点吗？
- Uh, is that what means the most to you?
呃，那对你来说最重要吗？
Then yes, we did.
那么是的，我们确实这么说了。
- So I really made a difference in your lives?
- 所以我真的在你们的生活中产生了影响吗？
- Is that what you need to hear to come back?
- 你需要听到这些才会回来吗？
Then yes.
那么是的。
- We promise to be better students.
- 我们承诺会成为更好的学生。
- And we'll try to get the rest of the class to be better too.
- 我们也会努力让班上其他同学变得更好。
- And we can honestly say
- 我们可以诚实地这么说
you're the best gym teacher we've ever had.
你是我们遇到过的最好的体育老师。
- For real. - Yup.
- 真的。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- All right, I'll come back.
好的，我会回来的。
[together] Yes!
太好了！
- Maybe I've been wrong about you Harpers all this time.
也许我一直以来对你们哈珀家的看法都是错的。
You're not such terrible kids.
你们并不是那么糟糕的孩子。
- That's the spirit!
这就对了！
- Now let's go get you some pudding to celebrate.
现在我们去拿些布丁庆祝一下。
[grunts] Come on, guys.
快点，伙计们。
Help me. This thing won't budge.
帮我一下，这东西动不了。
- Oh, that's because I locked the wheels.
哦，那是因为我锁了轮子。
Ahhhhhh!
啊！
- It's good that we're on the first floor.
- 幸好我们在一楼。
- We're on the second floor!
- 我们在二楼！
- Go, go, go!
- 快，快，快！
[all grunting]
[大家都在哼哼]
- Don't worry, Coach! We've got you!
- 别担心，教练！我们撑得住！
- Turns out he's right.
- 看来他说得对。
Physical fitness does matter.
- 体能确实很重要。
[grunting, straining]
[哼哼，用力]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪